<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Ben Broderick Phillips</title><link href="http://benbp.net/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://benbp.net/feeds/all-en.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://benbp.net/</id><updated>2013-08-19T00:00:00-07:00</updated><entry><title>Government Backed Public Keys</title><link href="http://benbp.net/gov-backed-pgp-key.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-08-19T00:00:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Ben Broderick Phillips</name></author><id>tag:benbp.net,2013-08-19:gov-backed-pgp-key.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://teddziuba.com/post/58735980543/how-the-nsa-could-stop-sucking-and-be-awesome-instead"&gt;Ted
Dziuba&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I already have federally-issued documentation of my citizenship, my US
Passport. There ought to be a way to get my PGP key signed by the government,
so I can sign my messages as an American citizen, having the government be the
trusted authority on that matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is interesting because it doesn’t compromise my privacy. My private key is
still private, but the government, through a verification process similar to
the passport process, has declared they trust me to be an American citizen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This could be added as a signal for NSA collection systems, since the NSA ought
to trust its own key-signing authority, it can be absolutely sure that an
encrypted communication it intercepts is from an American citizen, and thus
discard it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like this idea, with the emphasis on it being an opt-in service. 
Obviously one issue is that it would make it even easier to track
WHO we are communicating to. However, since the NSA already does this easily,
preventing them from doing so has to be accomplished by regulation and
oversight, not by technological safeguards.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Lunch with the Financial Times</title><link href="http://benbp.net/lunch-with-times.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-08-19T00:00:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Ben Broderick Phillips</name></author><id>tag:benbp.net,2013-08-19:lunch-with-times.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Despite it's occasional snoodiness, the article series Lunch with the Financial
Times will make both your brain and your mouth salivate. I think what I like
most about it is the interesting opinions that get mentioned only in passing,
leaving you to do the unraveling:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ft.com/intl/cms/s/2/a55ffe5e-00e0-11e3-8918-00144feab7de.html"&gt;Carolina
Herrera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s quite useful to have your children in the company,” says Herrera. “They
tell you immediately if they don’t like something.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ft.com/intl/cms/s/2/1e3fbcca-f9c4-11e2-b8ef-00144feabdc0.html"&gt;Jeremy
Deller&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flustered by all the comings and goings, I find myself asking Deller whether he
is interested in “relational aesthetics”, a term coined by French art critic
Nicolas Bourriaud to describe the kind of artwork that, like Deller’s, might be
said to create a kind of community. Deller, who started to shake his head at
“relational”, says that reading art theory makes him anxious but admits he
thinks good art shouldn’t try to do anything useful, and doesn’t like the way
art gets co-opted by politicians to solve social problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>The Ecuadorean Library</title><link href="http://benbp.net/bruce-sterling-ecuadorean.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-08-11T00:00:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Ben Broderick Phillips</name></author><id>tag:benbp.net,2013-08-11:bruce-sterling-ecuadorean.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;For anyone following the recent NSA leaks, &lt;a href="https://medium.com/geek-empire-1/a1ebd2b4a0e5"&gt;this
essay&lt;/a&gt; by Bruce Sterling
provides what you might call a theatrical portrayal of the situation. It is at
once wildly insightful, humorous, despairing, and hopeful. Do read.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can tell that Manning, Assange and Snowden are all the same kind of
irritant, because, somehow, amazingly, the planet’s response is to physically
squish them. They’re all online big-time, and their digital shadow is huge, so
the response is just to squeeze their mortal human bodies, literally, legally,
extra-legally, by whatever means becomes available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/geek-empire-1/a1ebd2b4a0e5"&gt;Bruce Sterling - The Ecuadorian Library&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>First Post</title><link href="http://benbp.net/first-post.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-07-28T00:00:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Ben Broderick Phillips</name></author><id>tag:benbp.net,2013-07-28:first-post.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is either the beginning of a long blogging journey, or an optimistic
first post on yet another site that I will create and eventually abandon to the
depths of the internet. I hope it is the former. Here is what you can expect to
hear from me should you decide to follow this blog:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intellectual musings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awesome videos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feats of expository bravado&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Horribly embarassing opinions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How-to guides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Links galore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cute animal pictures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beer recommendations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To start off, I will exercise list item 2 (awesome videos), and share with you
one of my favorite videos of all time, 
&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=65PqQCaJTeM"&gt;GOLDEN POWER&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>